altn.com 2018-07-28

# Alt-N Technologies: Privacy Policy

MDaemon Technologies is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out MDaemon Technologies' policy with respect to our collection, use, and disclosure of personal information.

## Contact Information

MDaemon Technologies welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that we have not adhered to this Policy or if you wish to review or edit your personal information, please contact us by e-mail at [webmaster@mdaemon.com](mailto:webmaster@mdaemon.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy), and we will use reasonable commercial efforts to address any concerns that you may have.

## Collection Of Personal Information

In your dealings with MDaemon Technologies you may provide MDaemon Technologies with personal information. Personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy means information that personally identifies you or that can be used together with other information to personally identify you. We also may use "cookies" from time to time to help personalize your online experience with us. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer to help us make your visit to our site more "user friendly. Cookies provide us with information about your use of the site that can help us improve the site and your experience with it. Any personal information collected about you through cookies will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you should receive a warning message with each cookie. You may refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser, however you should be aware that our site like most other popular sites may not work well with "cookies disabled."

## Use And Disclosure Of Personal Information

Except as part of the sale of all or substantially all of the assets of MDaemon Technologies, MDaemon Technologies will not sell, trade or rent your personal information to any third party unless we have your consent. We will only use and/or disclose personal information in order for:

  1. the internal use of MDaemon Technologies, including, without limitation:
    * understanding and meeting your needs and preferences
    * developing new and enhancing existing services and product offerings, and
    * managing and developing MDaemon Technologies' business and operations;
  2. any purpose related to the billing, activation, provision, maintenance, deactivation and/or your use of MDaemon Technologies' products and/or services;
  3. providing you with upgrades and/or updates of the software and/or third party products and/or services and notice of upgrades and/or updates of the software and/or third party products and/or services;
  4. any purposes permitted or required by any applicable law; and/or
  5. any other purposes which are included in your agreements with MDaemon Technologies.

We also reserve the right to use, disclose, sell, trade or rent data aggregated provided that the data cannot personally identify any individual.

Except where we are required by law to disclose personal information, we will require any person to whom we provide your personal information to agree to comply with applicable privacy laws; however we will have no liability to you if any person fails to do so.

To be able to serve you, your personal information may be collected, stored and/or processed, or otherwise used by or on our behalf both inside and outside of the United States of America and Canada by third party service providers or by MDaemon Technologies, to perform functions on our behalf. As a result, that country's courts, governments, or law enforcement agencies could obtain disclosure of such information under that country's laws.

## Security Of Your Personal Information

Our site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized alteration of the information under our control. More specifically, we use SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive personal information such as credit card information.

## Fraud

WARNING: We take fraud seriously. It is a crime to purchase products with a false name or with the use of an invalid credit card - one that is created for the sole purpose of purchasing items illegally or using a credit card or its information, via theft or unauthorized use. It is also illegal to misuse the charge back process to take advantage of merchants. If you are a perpetrator of fraud, be aware that we will actively pursue and prosecute fraud offenders to the fullest extent of the law.

Although most fraud offenders use free email services and false names, many are not aware that their web browser transmits a unique Internet address to us which can be used by law enforcement officials to identify and locate them. We will work with cardholders, credit card companies, and enforcement authorities to pursue fraud offenders.

We will submit all fraudulent orders sent to us to The United States Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and the International Criminal Police Organization (INTERPOL) for prosecution to the fullest extent of the law.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

MDaemon Technologies will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback or changes to privacy legislation. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how MDaemon Technologies is protecting your personal information.

## Withdrawal Of Consent

Except as required by law, we will not use or disclose your personal information for any purpose for which you refuse us consent or later withdraw your consent. If you withdraw consent, you agree that in spite of this withdrawal we may continue to use the personal information previously provided to us to the extent that we are contractually obligated to do so and to the extent necessary to enforce any contractual obligations you may have to MDaemon Technologies. You also understand that although you can use our site for some purposes without providing us with any personal information, we need personal information about you for some services, including those that require payment or involve an ongoing relationship with MDaemon Technologies or our partners. If you refuse to provide us with the information we require or later withdraw your consent to use and disclose this information, we may no longer be able to provide you with these services.

Current Version: 2.1  
Date Updated: January 02, 2018
